[{"answer": "We don't know what's there.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Anything yet?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "You know I think the best clues that we have come from the neighbors.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "And Nic, given all what you've found out there, I mean is it -- is it credible that no one at any high government level or military level in Pakistan had a clue that bin Laden was in this compound?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "Well, you know, obviously, I was elated the SEALs, you know, were involved, and at the pointy edge, but also, you know, I look at it and I understand it's a team effort.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "When you saw the detail of this operation, what were your thoughts?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, these guys are pros.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "I mean do you care either way?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 99, "question": "But from your point of view, is this the stuff that you train for?", "qSentId": 98}, {"answer": "It wouldn't have bothered me a bit, Piers.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "Would it have bothered you in that situation whether he was armed or not?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, just look at the basic training.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Why are they special?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Well, you know, as Ryan had mentioned, one of the most important things, is that these guys had been trained time and time again, and so they have built up a level of inoculation to stress, so that they're able to rely on their training in those moments.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "What goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Well, I hope not.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Are we ever going to know who they are?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's surprising that the numbers have remained relatively stable.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Is that what you would hope would happen?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "It's a very special day.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "I mean to take out bin Laden and the fact that it was a SEAL team that did this, pretty special day?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Why, I think as we've indicated during the course of the last several days, we're making some consideration of the potential ramifications of the release of any such photos.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "What is the current situation with regard to those?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "I've seen some pictures, yes.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "I mean one final question with regard to the pictures, have you actually seen them yourself?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "I'm not going to get into trying to describe them.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "ORGAN: And what do they depict?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "No, we weren't able to see video footage from the scene.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Were you able to actually see any video footage from the scene as it happened?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "He has not yet, no.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Do you know if the president had spoken directly to the Navy SEALs involved in this mission yet?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "I anticipate he will.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Does he plan to?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I think they'll have an opportunity to talk directly to them.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "What kind of thing would you imagine he'd say?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Well, it's not a matter of trust, it's a matter of finding common interests and working together with them.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "I mean, how can you trust them after this?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Well, it's kind of a perfect hypothetical, Piers, that I'm going to not -- I'm going to choose to not answer.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "If Pakistan was hunting a terrorist who had killed over 3,000 of their people and they discovered after 10 years that he was residing in a compound right next to an American military base where your senior intelligence people were also working, they'd be entitled to be pretty cheesed off, wouldn't they?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "My personal reaction was threefold.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "And finally, what was your personal reaction the moment you heard that the mission was successful and bin Laden was dead?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "Well, that's exactly what the president said, but that spontaneity is not my strong suit, and spontaneity is not a big characteristic in the situation room.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "I mean I don't doubt for a moment that all those thoughts were in your mind, but I kind of hoped for a slightly more spontaneous one-liner when you heard that he was dead, something along the lines of \"got him\" or something?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "This is not a major with me, but I have spoken to people who have seen the pictures.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Would you release them?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I agree.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "I mean, it's the same thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "Let me say, first of all, I don't consider it torture.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "And do you believe, if that's the case, that vindicate the case for interrogation methods like waterboarding?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Two things, one, Navy SEALS are waterboarded as part of their training.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Would you have been perfectly happy for them to be waterboarded and put through all the other things that you think are perfectly acceptable for the people at, say, Guantanamo Bay?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "ING: No, I've spoken to people on the ground, people who were involved in that.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "So how effective is it?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "We've always considered it torture.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "I think it's called plausible deniability, where John Yoo, who wrote the memo, said, look, I'm just a lawyer; I didn't make the decision.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "I mean, President Bush insisted that he did it within the law, and that if it hadn't been deemed lawful, he wouldn't have authorized it?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "First of all, I think waterboarding is torture.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Where is the line drawn as far as you're concerned?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "I don't think it should be used, but I think we ought to know that we are sacrificing a great deal.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "If it works, should you use it?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "I am not in favor of it, but I understand why many Americans would favor it.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Are you in favor of it, then, or not?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "If you bought into the last administration's argument that everyone at Guantanamo was the worst of the worst, the kind of people that would chew through the hydraulic lines of the airplane to kill Americans, then maybe waterboarding perhaps would not be considered unacceptable.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "How do you get this kind of information out of implacable enemies who are prepared to dies for their cause, if you're not going to use some form of aggressive interrogation?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I agree.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "What do you do to get that information out of them?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "I don't -- as someone mentioned earlier, I don't think there's any debate about the fact that he's dead.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "What I want to ask you both very quickly -- let me start with you, colonel, should we publish the picture of a dead Osama bin Laden?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Well, he's gotten a measure of credit, which he deserves.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "The flip side of the commander in chief making the decision that he did, and being rightly credited for it, is that that decision was predicated on policies that he reviled.", "docId": "110503pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "What's your gut feeling request?", "qSentId": 515}]